{
    "subject": "resource/Louis,_Duke_of_Burgundy",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Son",
    "human_readable": "Louis, Duke of Burgundy is a Son.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9205619692802429,
            "question": "Who was Louis, Duke of Burgundy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7629292607307434,
            "question": "Was Louis, Duke of Burgundy's lineage royal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5937724113464355,
            "question": "To what title did Louis, Duke of Burgundy claim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5441933870315552,
            "question": "Did Louis, Duke of Burgundy have any notable descendants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5344662666320801,
            "question": "Can you name any other prominent figures from the same era as Louis, Duke of Burgundy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5280056595802307,
            "question": "What historical period did Louis, Duke of Burgundy live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5045425295829773,
            "question": "What are some primary sources about the life and times of Louis, Duke of Burgundy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46994438767433167,
            "question": "Were there any significant events or conflicts associated with Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3743046820163727,
            "question": "What role did Louis, Duke of Burgundy play in shaping history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36578330397605896,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Louis and his father?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Louis, Duke of Burgundy is a Son.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3619_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Louis, Duke of Burgundy play in shaping history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3619_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant events or conflicts associated with Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3619_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some primary sources about the life and times of Louis, Duke of Burgundy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3619_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3619_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To answer the question \"Louis, Duke of Burgundy is a Son\", I will search for evidence in the provided context information.\n\nAfter reviewing the documents, I found several mentions of Louis, Duke of Burgundy being referred to as:\n\n* The eldest son of Louis, Grand Dauphin (document 1)\n* The eldest son of Louis, Dauphin of France and Maria Anna Victoria of Bavaria (documents 3, 5, 7)\n* The son of Louis, le Grand Dauphin, who was the grandson of Louis XIV of France and Navarre (document 6)\n\nBased on this information, I can conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Louis, Duke of Burgundy being the son of the Grand Dauphin and grandson of King Louis XIV. Therefore, the triple stating that \"Louis, Duke of Burgundy is a Son\" is supported by the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}